The seven gates of Jahanam, a circumflex euros, a korei euros trade, and reminder, sources
read quietly slash show on screen as text, korei euros trade, and 1544, a circumflex euros,
a circumflex euros, oh it has seven gates, for every gate is of them a portion designated
dot a circumflex euros, sahi international, korei euros trade, and 5030, a circumflex euros,
a circumflex euros, oh we will say to hell, a circumflex euros are you fully eurostrade
and it will say, a circumflex euros are there any more a eurostrade a circumflex euros,
korei euros trade, and 3971 a circumflex euros, 72 a circumflex euros groups led to hell
and to paradise, script duration, the korei euros trade and warns us about Jahanam with
clarity and purpose, in sura alayuro's hair, ala says about hell, a circumflex euros
oh it has seven gates, for every gate is of them a portion designated dot a circumflex
euros each gate is just to see euros no soul is wronged, Jahanam is not a story to scare,
but a reality to prepare for, on the day of judgment groups will be led to euros some
to punishment and some to mercy, ala will even say to hell, a circumflex euros oh are
you fully euros and it will reply, a circumflex euros oh are there any more euros the scene
is heavy, and eat a eurostrade as meant to wake our hearts, what protects us, faith that
is lived, not just said, prayer on time, charity that softens the heart, truth on the tongue,
patience in hardship, and repentancy euros returning to ala again and again, no one who
turns back to ala loses by it, today choose one step, pray your next prayer with focus,
forgive someone or give in charity for ala yurostrade as sake, ask ala to keep you far
from the gates of Jahanam and near to the gates of Jahanam, oh ala, save us from the fire and
make us steadfast upon truth and patience, ameen, subscribe for more a circumflex euros oh words
of korei euros rade and insuna dot a circumflex euros